This is a great day.
We're having our second
lecture on glass,
and we've got a demo--
where did Peter go?
So we've got a demo
coming up for you
from the director of the
glass blowing lab here at MIT.
And now before we
start, I just want
to mention, so next Monday--
so we're going to talk today--
we're going to continue
what we started, which
is the chemistry
of glass, and we'll
talk about that cooling curve or
the effects of different things
on the glass formation
and then how to engineer
the properties of the glass.
Before I start, I just want
to mention that next Monday we
have something called
the Wulff Lecture.
And this is a lecture that
is open to the public.
It's geared towards freshmen.
It's put on by the Department
of Materials Science
and Engineering every
year, and it's usually
some sort of really interesting,
exciting topic and usually
a very dynamic lecture.
And in this case it's one of
our very own, Sam Shames, who
graduated in 2014, and he'll
be talking about his adventures
as a material
scientist and how he's
used that knowledge in his
life and also in the company
that he founded which is now
selling products in over 70
countries around the world.
So I think that will
be a lot of fun.
If you can make it, it's next
Monday from 4:00 to 5:00 PM.